// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "How many vowels are there in english alphabets",
    answer: "5",
    options: [
      "4",
      "5",
      "7",
      "9"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Identify vowel from options",
    answer: "e",
    options: [
      "d",
      "f",
      "e",
      "s"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "The consonants in the word \"CAT\" are :",
    answer: "C,T",
    options: [
      "C,T",
      "A,T",
      "A",
      "C,A"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "The vowels in the word \"RUN\" are :",
    answer: "U",
    options: [
      "N",
      "R",
      "N,R",
      "U"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Count the total number of vowels present in the word : \"MISSISSIPPI\" ",
    answer: "4",
    options: [
      "7",
      "4",
      "11",
      "2"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "From given options which is not vowel",
    answer: "d",
    options: [
      "e",
      "i",
      "d",
      "u"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "How many consonants are there in english alphabets ",
    answer: "21",
    options: [
      "26",
      "5",
      "25",
      "21"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Count the total number of consonants and vowels in word \"SCHOOL\" ",
    answer: "Consonants 4,Vowels 2",
    options: [
      "Consonants 3,Vowels 3",
      "Consonants 5,Vowels 1",
      "Consonants 4,Vowels 2",
      "Consonants 2,Vowels 4"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "From given options which is not consonant",
    answer: "e",
    options: [
      "e",
      "x",
      "d",
      "r"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Find the odd one out ",
    answer: "u",
    options: [
      "x",
      "u",
      "g",
      "f"
    ]
  }
  
];
